Good morning.
Morning.
Dear Mr. Naoki Irie,
I am Kotoko Aihara, a senior in class F.
Your speech at the freshmen entrance ceremony
was so smart and cool,
that, for the past two years,
I've been in love with you.
But since classes are split by academic achievement,
and my grades are bad enough to land me in class F,
I've never been in class A with you and the smart kids before,
so, in my senior year, I've decided to
come clean and confess my feelings.
Irie, I love you.
Excuse me.
Will you please accept this letter?
No thanks.
You forgot a T.
There's a T missing.
Here, with a tea.
I hate stupid girls.
I forgot a T?
Oh no!
Itazura na Kiss: High School Chapter
She gave a love letter to Irie from class A!
Seriously?
What an idiot.
Kotoko!
Good morning Satomi, Jinko.
You really confessed your love to Irie?
He has an IQ of 200 and always
scores a 100% on tests.
And he's won every national tennis tournament he's entered!
He's irritatingly perfect.
Kotoko, count the alphabet on your fingers.
A, B, C, D, E...
F! See? F is on the other hand.
Class F is the class for losers.
Irie exists in a world different from ours.
I thought maybe there could be a
fraction of a chance he likes me.
Come on, no chance in a billion!
There are plenty of normal
guys who'd be a better match for you.
Kotoko!
It's Kinnosuke.
Kin!
You ignore me and confess your love to Irie?
It's not like I'm your girl.
Haven't we been sitting next to each other
for two years? That's ice cold!
Calm down.
Damn Irie, I can't stand how he embarassed you like that.
You're too worked up about it.
That's the bell, class.
Take your seats.
I'll be taking the attendance now.
Ikezawa.
Here.
Inoue.
Uchida.
Here.
Yamato.
Hanamura.
Since falling in love with
Irie in my freshman year,
I've been secretly checking
him out from time to time.
On the days I see him, I put a
heart sticker in my student calender.
But when I finally decided to confess...
No thanks.
My senior year began with
a rejected love letter.
I guess I should give up
on that cold-hearted guy.
My poor little letter.
Let's eat!
I am so hungry!
Kotoko!
Kin.
Your family is moving soon right?
When's it happening? I wanna help.
Thanks, Kin.
But we already moved all our furniture yesterday.
I see...
How about a housewarming party?
The thing is, we're renovating the kitchen
and the gas is still shut off. So—
No problem!
We'll just bring food. Right?
I'm in!
Yeah!
Catch you later. Love you Kotoko!
See you later!
Pushy as always.
Well, he is trying to cheer you up
after what happened this morning.
He is?
He's being considerate, in his own way.
Nicer than you'd expect.
You should forget the ice
guy settle for Kinnosuke.
Kotoko and Kin, a perfect match.
Even so...
No matter how it turned out, it was a bad idea
to give a letter to a guy you've never talked to.
Yeah, anyone would be shocked.
It wasn't really sudden.
We've had a serious chat before.
A serious chat?
Yes!
A year ago, after an exam...
How did you do on English?
I got a 38. How about you?
The same, basically.
You, Jinko?
I flunked. Who cares? I'll
marry a Japanese guy anyway.
Hey, let's forget it and
go eat some ice cream!
Good idea.
Party!
Par...
My test!
Kotoko...
Japanese!
English!
Missing math! Math, math...
There it is!
Is this yours?
Yes, I got a 27 on it.
Thank you for picking it up.
What an idiot.
At long last! A real conversation with Irie!
Your imagination is definitely askew.
Seriously. It's working overtime.
I'm just being positive.
Really?
Look!
Your positive counterpart is waiting for you.
Off we go!
What a cool looking house!
It's really traditional, isn't it?
Dad got it from a friend at a low price.
I really wanted a western
one with bow windows.
Hey dad, I'm home!
Hiya! Kotoko, welcome home.
Congratulations on your new home!
Jinko and Satomi, pretty as always.
Now, come in.
Thank you.
Make yourselves at home! Come on in!
Now, everyone, let's eat.
Thank you for the food.
Dig in.
Thanks.
Road Work
Go ahead and start.
Yes, sir!
Y'know, if the gas was working, I could've
made a feast for you kids! Sorry to trouble you.
No, no, don't apologize.
We'll enjoy your pro cooking some other time!
Thanks.
Not at all.
Mr. Aihara, we're starting on the gas line.
Yeah, please.
Earthquake?
That is too solid!
Hey, don't slack off.
That wasn't an earthquake, right?
Maybe it was the construction work!
Nonsense. You're a pretty funny guy!
Listen up, this house is from
when they built stuff to last!
Everyone, run!
But... but it's supposed to be sturdy!
Dad, hurry! Hurry up!
Kotoko!
Your mom!
Kotoko, go!
Dad, hurry up!
Get clear! This is dangerous!
Hurry!
Move it!
Stop! Stop!
Stop drilling!
Stop the drilling! Enough!
I said stop drilling!
Hey you, hey!
What's up?
The shaking from the the drill
damn near shook the house apart!
No way!
Run!
How did you feel when it happened?
I...I...was shocked.
Never seen anything like it before.
It's a miracle no one was hurt.
Yes, I...
At 6 P.M. yesterday, Mr.
Shigeo Aihara's house
Drill's Vibrations Cause House to Collapse
in Suginami, Tokyo was met with disaster
caused by drilling to access a nearby gas line.
Wow, look at that!
Termites At Work?
Kotoko.
Good morning.
Morning.
Seems like you're always
the center of attention, lately.
This is how it feels to
want to crawl under a brick.
You mean a rock, right?
Everyone, listen up!
Kotoko Aihara's house was destroyed yesterday,
so we're looking for
donations to help her out!
Is that Kin?
Is he crazy?
Please give whatever you can! I'm begging you!
Stop, Kin!
Tragedy hits and still she comes to school!
I said stop! You stupid dummy!
I'm doing this for you.
Whatever!
You're in the way.
What's that supposed to mean?
Whose fault do you think this is?
Whoever was manning that drill?
Say what?
Kotoko didn't have a bad
luck streak until you shot her down!
Are you suggesting I made the pillars crack?
Damn right! Your rotten
heart rotted her pillars.
Fine.
I'll donate to stop your complaining.
Don't insult me!
I'll die before taking your charity.
Are you really in a position to refuse?
Of course I am.
I see.
The last thing I want is to owe you anything!
What are you laughing at?
Don't make a fool out of me,
just because I'm stupid!
I'll show him I'm no fool.
You'll see!
My name is getting on the
scoreboard after this next test!
Kotoko, you gotta make
the top 100 for that.
No one in class F has done that.
Not in the history of Tonan High School!
Are you sane right now?
Watch me make history.
The object is experiencing
a centripetal force.
This establishes the formula.
Do you understand?
Impossible.
Never imagined termites
could've eat the pillars apart.
You being on the news has
made me a laughing stock.
Well, after I was on TV, Iri contacted me.
Who's Iri?
My best friend, who's putting us up.
We were in junior high school together.
Guy was a genius, went to Tokyo University.
You and his eldest son are the same age.
And go to the same...
Here! Please stop here!
This is where we get out.
Wow! What an incredible house!
They even have a pool!
He's the CEO of a big company.
I'm proud of him.
Kotoko, ring the bell.
Sure.
Irie...?
No way!
What's taking you?
Ring it already.
Y-yeah.
Ai!
Iri! It's been ages!
I've been waiting to roll out
the welcome wagon for you two!
Well, where is it?
You're so mean!
You could've asked me to pick you up.
I'm already imposing on you, too much.
Come on, what are friends for?
My daughter.
You must be Kotoko.
You look just like your mom. So pretty.
You don't look like him. That's a relief.
Huh?
Nothing... Thank you for everything.
My pleasure. Come in.
Thanks.
You lose weight?
About 5 kg.
We're coming in!
Sorry to trouble you.
Hey, they're here! Come introduce yourselves.
Nao!
"Nao"?
I'm Naoki, the eldest son.
Nice to meet you.
That s fine  son you got there, Iri!
No way!
What's wrong, Kotoko?
I-I guess I ended up owing you, after all...
Do you two know each other?
We're in nowhere near the same class, but
we've recently become acquainted.
That's right!
They were like peas in a pod this morning.
Who took those?
Honestly, mother...
Come in, Aihara, and make yourself comfortable.
Well, if you insist.
Please.
Come in.
Thank you.
Please dig in.
Here.
Aren't you a pretty girl?
It's going to be nice having
some company around here!
Ma'am, we lost everything.
Your kindness is appreciated.
It's our pleasure. I'm just glad
to have another girl around!
We only have boys.
Whoa, you scared me.
Oh, Yuki.
This is Kotoko. Introduce yourself.
I'm Yuki Irie, third year
elementary school student.
Nice to meet you, Yuki.
I'm studying kanji. Can you help me?
Kanji for third graders? I can handle that!
It's this part.
Uh... river horse? Sea sun? And nut mouse, I think.
What're you, stupid?
Those are hippo, starfish, and squirrel.
You suck!
Yuki, that's unacceptable. Apologize now.
That kid!
I'm so sorry about my boy.
Sorry, Kotoko.
Let me show you to your room.
I worked hard decorating it.
Come on.
Go ahead.
This way, come on.
Follow me.
Here you go!
Well?
It's cute!
Like it?
Yes.
That's great!
I always wanted a daughter to
share girly things with!
Also...
Surprise!
They're gorgeous!
They're all for you. Wear whatever you like.
Why so many?
This was Yuki's room.
His stuff is in my room.
It's cramped, as you'd imagine.
You're his big brother,
so stop making such a fuss!
Kotoko, come with me.
Never mind what he says, okay?
Okay...
Naoki.
Help us unpack these gifts I bought for her.
Come on, come on.
You two go to the same school,
so try to get along.
Now, please excuse me.
Yuki, come with me.
Well, what do you need me to do?
Don't bother. I'll do it myself.
Oh, that's right.
I seem to recall you not wanting to owe me anything.
Just so you know, you being here
makes no difference to me either way.
Just stay out of my hair.
Idiot.
He really does have ice
running through his veins.
How the heck did I end up here?
Here's to termites!
You lose weight?
The termintes got to me.
Here's to termites!
Kotoko.
Put your things away?
Oh... yes.
I'm coming in.
The men have started drinking.
Why don't we have tea?
What's wrong? You seem down.
Oh, I'm just tired.
You must be.
You've gone through a lot.
Exhausted, huh?
This is your room now, feel free to relax.
Come with me.
Why don't you take off your jacket?
Thank you.
Here you are.
Don't worry what Naoki said, okay?
He can be such a sourpuss.
You wouldn't believe it,
but he used to be so adorable.
He was?
Sure was.
I know. Let me show you something amazing!
Hold on.
Kotoko, thanks for waiting.
I've always wanted to show this to someone.
Are these pictures of Naoki?
Take a peek.
What an adorable girl.
I know.
Actually...
It's Naoki.
He looks just like a girl!
I really wanted a baby girl.
To be honest, I was shocked to have a boy.
And since it would've been a shame
to let the clothes go to waste...
I made him wear them until he refused.
Even Yuki doesn't know.
It'll be our little secret.
For sure.
Adorable.
I know.
Check out the flower.
Here, Papa.
Thanks, Mama.
Come to my restaurant next time you can.
I'll make you all the pufferfish you want!
Seriously, Ai?
I'll be there in a puff!
Mom.
She's acting weird.
Don't stare, Yuki.
Kotoko, what's wrong? Are you sick?
Oh, no. It's nothing.
Kotoko, did you sleep well last night?
Yes.
From today, this is your home, okay?
Yes, thank you.
You can marry into the family too.
Uh, well, she's still just in high school.
He's right.
Iri, thank you so much again.
My pleasure.
I should get going.
Thanks for breakfast.
See you.
Oh, look at the time.
I've put lunch boxes in
Naoki's and Kotoko's bags.
Kotoko, you two headed
the same way, go with him.
Oh, sure.
Hurry up.
Gone in a puff!
Naoki, show her the way, okay?
Thanks for the meal. We're heading out.
Me too!
No!
You finish your meal.
Let them go alone, okay?
Back to breakfast.
When are you gonna get home today?
I've got practice, so probably not until six.
Aihara.
Yes?
Don't walk beside me.
Learn the route to school, today.
And promise me three things.
No one can know we live together,
no talking to me at school,
and stay 3 steps, no, 3 meters back
when we walk outside together.
Isn't that kind of excessive?
I don't want any weird rumors getting around.
As I said, I hate stupid girls.
I'll have my revenge one day!
Kotoko, let's hang out this afternoon.
Can't. I have to study for the test.
Seriously?
You're serious about
making class F history?
I will.
Aihara.
Grab your bag and come with me.
Whoa, whoa, what's the
hotshot from class A want?
What? Wait a sec.
Stop, don't go with him. Stop! Stop!
What?
Mom put the wrong lunchbox in my bag.
Oh, she did.
For someone who doesn't want to talk,
you broke your own rule already.
What else was I supposed to do?
Wires have gotten crossed from living together.
I agree.
Maybe you'll get so confused
you'll wear my skirt.
Why would I do that?
Ta-da!
Irie, aren't you the cutest?
Where did you get that?
A gift from your mom.
Even a genius has a weak point.
Enough, give it back.
Fine.
If you'll make a deal.
You're blackmailing me?
Sure am!
Tutor me for the exam.
Get me on the board, and I'll give it back.
I refuse. It'd take divine
intervention to manage that.
Say no and I'll copy it and the whole school...
Fine.
We're starting tonight. All night long.
And it's going to be harsh.
So brace yourself.
Harsh...?
Here she comes.
Yo, yo, yo, what was that about?
Is something going on with you and Irie?
Kotoko?
Oh, nothing.
Now, it's time for me to hit the books!
Hi, I'm back.
Welcome home!
How did it go with you two?
You didn't each lunch together?
No...
Even after I set up an excuse?
I mean, you know how Naoki acts.
You'll need to get aggressive with him.
Aggressive to what end?
Oh, welcome home, Naoki!
I can't believe you got the
lunches mixed up. Get it together.
Everyone makes mistakes.
Right?
Here's hoping Naoki
will make a certain mistake soon.
Thanks for the meal.
Are you done already?
You're young, eat more.
I've got to start studying for an exam.
What? You're going to study?!
That's the spirit. I'll bring you snacks.
Thank you.
Bring enough for me.
Are you going to study with Kotoko?
Is that a problem?
That is incredible!
Naoki actually studying! And it's all
thanks to Kotoko, right, Papa?
You realize this is your fault, right?
Whatever do you mean?
Naoki, teach me, too.
You're at the top of your class
already. There's no point.
What don't you understand, exactly?
I don't understand what
parts I don't understand.
I'd be curious to see what your brain looks like.
Why do you even go to school?
Well, shouldn't I be going because I'm dumb?
Irie, how do you study?
I don't. I memorize
everything I see and hear.
You really are a genius.
Whatever. Finish the problem.
Let's see... the volume's proportional
to the cubed radius, right?
And then...
Can't you think without talking?
Review the fundamentals. What's pi?
Pi?
Well, I wouldn't expect anything in return.
It's 3.14! Just like White Day!
Come on!
Sorry. Am I interrupting?
What do you think you're doing?!
Because you two look so lovely.
Wanted it on the record!
Would you get out?
Oh, am I a third wheel? Sorry about that.
Here are the snacks.
You two are a perfect match.
Hurry up and get married!
Would you stop spouting
idiotic nonsense?!
Come on, let's get this over with.
Okay.
Hey.
Can I use this?
Sure.
The pen too.
Listen up. There are only five days left.
We can't review everything in detail.
Try these exercises I made.
Okay.
You need to memorize these formulas.
Manage that and you'll
at least score an 80. Got it?
Okay.
You need this for that question.
Just like the first one.
Wrong.
"Attitude."
"Behavior."
"Looking forward to i-n-g."
Mr. Aihara, Papa, enjoy your class reunion.
We'll be back tomorrow night.
We'll grab lots of souvenirs.
Sure.
Then,
off we go!
Take care.
See ya.
See you.
They seem excited.
I hope the food will be good. Oh!
Hello, Irie household.
Suzuko, it's been a while. How are you?
What? You're on a flight
coming from America?
It's always sudden with you.
I can't just drop everything to...
Okay.
Got it. Fukuoka Airport.
Right. Right. I understand. Of course.
Yuki!
We're spending the night out.
Get your things together.
Kotoko, can I talk to you for a sec?
Sure.
Could you house-sit?
Is something wrong?
My mother lives in Kyushu and
it seems she's in poor health.
My sister is headed
over from America to see her.
I'm sorry to hear that.
It's nothing serious but
But I want to visit her too.
So, Can you house-sit?
Yes, of course.
I'll take Yuki since he's still little.
Okay.
Thanks. The house is in your hands.
Just you...
And Naoki.
Right. Just us.
Just us?!
Naoki, I'm counting on you.
Fine, I don't care.
Well, Kotoko, we're off.
O-okay.
Naoki, take care of things.
Yeah.
See ya!
See you.
Take care.
Bye.
Hey.
Yes?
No afternoon classes on Saturday.
We'll start studying at three.
Come straight home. Got it?
Okay.
Also,
you handle dinner tonight.
Sure.
Fukuoka Airport International Flights
Rika!
Hey again, Yuki.
It's been a while, sis.
You look well, Suzuko.
You really love calling
out of the blue, don't you?
And you always love doing
stuff without letting anyone know.
Naoki didn't come?
He's studying.
Naoki? Study?
Huh.
I'm gonna be late.
...3 meters back...
American schools have such
long summer holidays.
Three whole months!
I'll take Rika to see the folks
in Saga and then go to Europe.
Sounds wonderful.
No umbrella?
If I did, it wouldn't rain.
I was right there. You should
have asked to share mine.
Would you if I asked?
Good question.
Ever hear of "shelter from the storm"?
I have!
But... I promised.
What promise?
I didn't want to be late
for our study session.
I'll go get changed.
Hold it.
Don't waltz through
the house soaking.
Shower first.
We'll study after dinner.
Thank you.
Irie...
So Naoki and this Kotoko are
together all alone now?
That they are.
By this time, I bet they're...
My, oh my!
Eek!
Oh my.
Oh no.
I forgot to bring my underwear.
A-cup, huh?
I wouldn't make a move on that.
I wish we were together every day.
Wanna know how to make that happen?
Huh, how?
I just have to marry Naoki.
You and my brother?
After I've grown up.
Will you help me?
I will!
It will be our secret until then.
Stewed Pork
A woman's inner beauty is most important.
I'll show off my domestic
skills with pork and curry.
He'll be speechless.
"Simmer for two hours."
Physics is too hard.
The word "pulley" makes me wanna barf.
Huh?
Did I forget something...?
Hey, is dinner ready yet?
What the hell?
I was studying and forgot to check the pot.
And...
And then there was a disaster.
I'm sorry.
Wow! Is there anything you can't do?
Anyone can make curry.
It's strange. Curry is
supposed to be my specialty.
Get the pressure cooker.
Oh, okay.
It shortens the cooking time.
I didn't know that.
Give everyone my regards.
Don't forget our promise.
See ya, Rika.
Looks great!
Even I can make a salad.
Well? Looks good, huh?
The cucumbers.
Their shape is a little off, but...
I hate them.
Huh, so even you have preferences.
I'll eat them for you.
Thank you for the meal.
So good!
Irie, do you cook often?
This was the first time.
You know...
What now?
With just the two of us....
It's like we're newlyweds.
Or something.
Say...
There's something I'd like
you to teach me tonight.
What is it?
Physics.
Physics is just a report,
it's not on the test.
But...
You have no idea what you're doing.
Quite right!
No.
Why not?
I only promised to help you on the test.
Oh, come on.
Just review your notes.
Actually, I didn't take any notes.
I can't see!
Help! Irie, where are you?
I'm night blind, and I get
really nervous in the dark!
Hey, Irie?
Always overreacting.
But...
We can't study in the dark,
so let's start at five a.m., okay?
Okay.
I haven't slept enough
lately, so I'm going to bed.
You clean this up.
Okay.
I feel like a burglar.
Slowly...
I step...
Without making a sound!
Huh?
A burglar?
Notebook, notebook, physics notebook...
Got you.
What are you doing?
Uh, well, I'm not stealing anything!
Oh, I see. You aren't.
In that case...
you're here to make out, aren't you?
No!
I said I wouldn't make a move on you,
so you decided to take initiative, didn't you?
Stop!
Don't worry. I won't embarass you.
Irie, please don't.
Let's start out as friends!
Start out?
I've no interest in going out with you.
You were messing with me!
Hey.
Didn't you say you'd die
before taking my charity?
Then, what's this?
That's not charity.
I'm doing the favor of borrowing it from you.
I'll even let you help me copy it.
Got it? We start at five a.m.
I just wanted to copy it.
You won't learn anything that way.
Kotoko, I just got back. I brought you...
Oh my!
So lovely!
So cute!
Let's see. Like this?
Good.
I'm in.
Ready.
I'm off.
Okay.
Ko-to-ko.
Good luck with the exam.
For luck.
Thank you so much.
Now don't open it until
after you've finished.
Got it! See you later.
Take care.
You may now begin.
Midterm Examination Schedule
Day 1: Math, Modern Japanese
Day 2: English, Classical Japanese
Day 3: Japanese History, Chemistry
Time's up.
That's that!
Alright, let's blow off some steam!
Excuse me. Excuse me...
Excuse me.
Yes!
No.1: Naoki Irie - Score: 800
Irie, congratulations. You were
on top again. With a perfect score!
You did well.
Huh?
Didn't you see?
No way!
No.100: Kotoko Aihara - Score: 597
No.100!
I did it! I did! Irie, I really did it!
Aren't you embarrassed, shouting like that?
Thank you. I owe it all to you.
I'm not shaking hands.
You promised me something.
This?
It's not a flag, don't wave it around. Dammit...
Thanks again!
Don't push.
Something's up between them.
Oh my gosh, when did you take this?
What in the name of...
You and Irie?!
So lovey-dovey!
Oh boy...
Your dads are childhood friends?
What a coincidence.
So you're living in his house?
That's why you're always together.
And you did better on the test thanks to him.
So... do you share a room?
He's next door.
But you sleep in the same room?
No way!
How often do you have sex?
Never!
Really? How boring.
We only talk when studying.
So, he's ice at home too.
Yeah, and he hates me.
Poor Kotoko.
Make sure to keep this secret.
Roger.
Alright, let's actually go party, and cheer Kotoko up!
Kin, wait.
Come on!
Hey, Irie.
Do you think she's going out with him?
You okay with that?
None of my business.
She made the top 100.
She made Tonan High School history!
And she's in class F!
Aihara.
Come with me.
O...Okay.
Look.
What the heck?!
You took the words out of my mouth.
The rumored couple, currently living together:
3-A Naoki Irie, 3-F Kotoko Aihara
It's like all you do is trip me up.
I told you to stay out of my hair.
You're an utter annoyance.
I never cried before,
no matter how mean he was.
I...
can't help but like him.
I like him so much.
25th Tonan High School Sports Meet, in association with
Tonan University
It's a clear day for the Tonan
High School Sports Meet.
Presently, class F enjoys a large lead.
Will they come out on top once again this year?
Next up is the boys 100 meter
race, for the senior class.
Thanks, guys.
Hey, Irie.
I won't lose to you.
On your marks!
Set!
Yo! Yo! How does it feel?
F class's Ace Kinnosuke Ikezawa
Kin, great job!
How was it?
Great!
Kin, you're the best!
Hey!
I was a bit relieved to see you lose to Kin.
It shows you're human like us after all.
I am nothing like you.
What?
Why would I exert myself for a race like this?
Spoken like a sore loser.
Sore loser?
If you aren't, go on and prove
me otherwise in the mixed relay.
Fine, I'll show you what I can do.
We'll show you class F pride! We won't lose.
Keep at it, Kotoko.
Jinko, as the front runner,
give it all you got.
Where's this coming from?
Umezaburo, be in first place
when you pass me the baton.
I actually tend to cave under pressure...
But, okay!
Kin, you're our anchor!
Leave it to me.
Alright, let's go.
First runners, on your marks.
Now for the last event.
The seniors mixed relay.
On your marks!
Get set!
Go go, Jinko! Like that!
Keep it up!
Class F hands the baton off first.
It's up to you!
Yes!
F is in the lead! Behind them are class A and class E!
Kotoko!
F has an unquestioned lead
heading into the anchor hand off!
Victory is ours.
You're the loser this time, Irie.
Watch me. Watch...
Huh? Irie is staring at me.
Irie!
What's this?! Aihara has
passed the baton to Irie from class A!
Idiot.
What is she doing?
Is she stupid?
Kotoko, what are you doing? Hand it over!
Kin, sorry! Go for it!
The gap is narrowing!
Irie is getting closer! Ikezawa is desperate!
Kin, Irie!
A dead heat, each team is at the goal
line cheering their teammate on.
Don't jump onto the track, stupid.
Yo, Iridiot. What are
you doing on top of her?
Back off.
Who do you think you are?
If she'd passed the baton
correctly we would have won.
Spoken like a sore loser.
Those two...
Bro! Calm down!
They are a couple after all.
Kotoko's lucky.
Everyone is talking about us again.
I'm used to it.
It looks like Irie is carrying
Aihara to the nurse.
Hey.
How many times are you going
to watch your little candid video?
It's just so lovely.
Every day for three months
and you're still not done?
No, no, no, no.
Besides, the long-range video
camera your father bought is fantastic!
My pleasure.
Gotta say, that was a perfect angle.
You could do this professionally.
No, it's the subjects that are perfect.
Say, where's Kotoko?
She's always in her room.
Is that so?
Yup.
Irie will take the university
entrance exam tomorrow.
And then the one for Tokyo University.
He tutored me until I took the
exam for Tonan University.
I might not be of much help,
but I can hope that everything
goes smoothly for him!
Finished!
Papa.
Naoki! You sleep well last night?
Yeah, good morning.
Good.
He's so nervous you'd
think he's taking the exam.
Mama, it doesn't matter how good
your grades are, exams are a whole other beast!
When I took the exam, for Tokyo U my
mind went blank and then...
You alright, Naoki?
Oh my. He has a slight fever!
On today of all days!
Wait a sec! I'll bring something special.
Please.
Here, Irie. These always fix me
right up when I get sick.
Now, drink!
I'm relieved.
Great, he'll be alright.
Good luck, bro!
These don't cause drowsiness, do they?
An antihistamine...
What's that mean?
It works well, but with side effects.
Like?
Drowsiness.
Moron!
Irie, vomit! Vomit!
Gag yourself! Jam those fingers in!
It's alright.
It's my fault for trusting you.
Kotoko, what have you done?!
I'm so sorry, Irie!
Don't apologize, Kotoko.
It's the exam jinx.
I made a good luck charm. I'll go get it.
Get it hurry!
Ow, you stepped on my foot, girl!
Here it is!
It's so cute.
That should drive the jinx away!
I'll hook it to your bag.
It fell...
Kotoko! Don't jinx him even more!
Right. Sorry.
I nearly flopped!
Sorry, I know some words are
sensitive going into exams.
Idiot.
I'll be careful.
There.
Then, I'm off.
See ya!
See you!
Good luck!
Watanabe!
What?
My bag is stuck.
The charm got caught.
It's her fault...
What's this thing made of?
It won't budge a bit.
Hey, go on ahead of me.
And you?
I'll manage somehow.
Sorry. I'll be waiting for you.
Hey, Watanabe.
Hey, Irie, that's the first bell! Hurry!
National Center Test for
University Admissions
Sorry you had to wait.
I was worried.
Oh, you still have the charm.
It's bad luck. I'll remove it.
Oh, now it comes off.
You're the one who fell down the stairs?
Yes.
Hurry.
You have 20 minutes.
I'll take this.
The admission ticket.
Huh?
Son, I'm sure she means well,
but be sure to erase that.
Good luck!
Sorry.
That stupid...
Must have broken the fall.
Use mine.
Thanks.
Name: Yuuko Matsumoto
Name: Naoki Irie
10 minutes left.
Naoki!
What happened?
Irie!
The amulet didn't work?
Oh, it definitely did something!
I'm going to bed.
The answers will be in tomorrow's
newspaper. You check my score.
Good.
Another one.
Fantastic! A perfect score!
You really are a genius.
We'll have a celebration tonight.
Hooray!
Maybe I really am a genius.
It was all pure skill!
Hey, luck is a skill too!
Watanabe.
Irie's score was really something, huh?
Even class F is talking about it.
You took the exam with him, right?
I bet he only needed 20
minutes to solve them all!
Yeah, and your bad luck charm
made sure he only had twenty.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry.
Watanabe told me about the trouble
you had on the day of the test.
Maybe I'm nothing but bad luck for you.
You're right about that.
I'm the worst, for sure.
That is completely correct.
But...
It was fun, in a way.
That was the first time I can remember feeling nervous.
In a way, you gave me a valuable experience.
Alright, bad spirits are cast out.
Here's hoping the Tokyo U
exam goes off without a hitch!
I can't wait for you to enter my alma mater.
Well then, I'm off.
Naoki, do you have her good luck charm?
Do you want me to fail?
I'll see him off to the school.
Good idea. You don't mind, right?
Whatever. Just follow after me.
Kotoko, thanks.
Sure.
You always bring bad luck.
I've got the charm, so I'll
absorb all the bad luck. Relax!
Alright, we're here. That should satisfy you.
Bye.
Okay, good luck. You can do it!
I'm relieved. No trouble this time.
Huh? Where's the charm?
Did I drop it?
Oh, there it is.
Are you alright?
She just ran in front of my
car, but I didn't hit her.
She fell and hit her head.
Call an ambulance.
A-ambulance...
I can see the hospital.
It'll be faster to carry her.
Please call the police.
Yes.
Tokyo Sugimoto Hospital
As I slipped into unconsciousness,
all I could hear was his heartbeat.
Kotoko, Kotoko!
You had us all freaked out, dummy!
Kotoko, I'm glad you weren't hurt.
Huh? I...
Just a mild concussion.
You were lucky.
Ah, I almost hit the car and...
You're lucky to be alive.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
You're all here.
Didn't you go to the exam center?
I had to talk to the police.
You mean you didn't take
the exam for Tokyo University?
No, I didn't. Does it matter?
It matters of course!
Iri!
I'm terribly sorry.
What are you...
Come on, Ai, don't.
My silly daughter...
She put Naoki into this position.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Raise your head, Ai.
He chose not to go to the center.
He took Kotoko to the hospital, instead..
Saving her life is more important
than Tokyo University.
I'm really sorry.
That means...
you'll go to Tonan University too, right?
I suppose I will.
Good for you, Kotoko!
You'll be in the same school again this April!
Great! Great, great, great!
To the Irie family
To everyone in the Irie family. Thank you for everything.
Farewell.
Irie!
Running away?
Don't stop me.
I'm not.
Is this because of Tokyo University?
I really do just bring you bad luck.
I could have taken the
exam after the hospital.
Why didn't you?
I never really had a goal
in mind for Tokyo U,
and lately, I've been having
more fun around you.
Taking the escalator to
Tonan U doesn't sound so bad.
Are you saying you'll go
there because I'll be there?
Don't read too much into it.
I said what I wanted to say.
You can go now. Bye.
Ah, wait!
Wait.
I won't trouble you anymore,
can I please stay a little longer?
You will always be trouble.
Well, I can guarantee exciting days.
Getting cocky already, huh?
I guess. But...
Whatever. Get inside before my mom notices.
Okay, thanks.
Irie,
I still like you, okay?
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
It's finally graduation day.
Kotoko's graduating high school.
Your mom in heaven is happy.
Yeah, I think so.
It's good that you two will
attend the same university.
Right, Papa?
Yes, I guess.
I should be going.
Naoki.
It's your final day of high school.
Go together for once. Got it?
Now, have fun!
Right, enjoy!
Wait up, Irie.
It's our final day, let's walk together.
Time sure flies. We're graduating at last.
But y'know, out of all of high school,
this year was the best one,
since I could spend it with you!
It was the hardest year
in my 18 years of life.
Tonan University Affiliated High School - 25th Graduation Ceremony
That girl kept crying.
For real?
I was impressed with the principal's speech.
Right?
You were asleep, Kotoko.
We can finally say good-bye to class F.
So long to the curse of class F.
Three long years!
And Kotoko's long, one-sided love affair.
Girls! Congratulations on your graduation!
Thank you so much.
I'll take your picture.
Okay, say cheese!
Kotoko, look!
Naoki, come here.
Don't you have a gift for Kotoko?
Hell no.
How about the two of you in a—
Never.
Awww!
Irie, class F has a gift for you.
Drum roll! An Irie doll.
Thanks, I guess.
Most of class F was only able to graduate
because of the notes Kotoko borrowed from you.
Thus, the gift.
And...
Ta-da!
A Kotoko doll!
Cute!
But when?
We made them secretly.
What do you think? They're a set!
I don't like them at all.
Aren't you giving him something?
Yeah, um...I will, but...
It's not like you to hesitate.
You're always giving me stuff anyway.
He's right! Hand it over!
Well...
Irie...
Here...
Thanks.
He actually...
Accepted it.
Goodness, Naoki.
How about that picture, now?
Oh, sure. But just one, okay?
Kotoko, isn't this wonderful!
Come on!
Together! Real close, okay?
Back! Back!
Come on, get over here.
Kotoko, smile!
Did you know that in flower symbology,
a yellow tulip stands for...
Unrequited love?
No way!
Irie, you're a sadist!
Tonan High School
Senior F Class
What do you think? My own cooking! Eat up!
Enjoy, Kotoko!
Amazing, Kin! You're a good cook, huh?
Gonna make my way
in the world with these skills!
Ikeda. It's a shame about your entrance exam,
but I know you can make it as a chef!
I bet you'll be a famous one!
You bet. It's the first step in
Operation: "I Love Kotoko".
"I love Kotoko?"
I love you, Kotoko.
I'm so sorry I was in love with that other jerk!
It's alright.
Don't cry.
From now on, you can depend on me.
Kin, everything's set.
I'll now express my love
for Kotoko in a dance.
Please enjoy, Kotoko!
Ugh, class F is here too?
Oh no.
Come on, class A, look alive!
The same venue?
Hey look, it's class A!
Seriously?
I want to congratulate class A on it's graduation.
Your brilliance has made me proud.
Many of you  will be entering Tokyo University,
and that is another source of pride.
Youth is not all about study.
These kids have been insulted as failures,
but their ability to withstand that is worth praise.
Intelligence only means so much.
It's more important to have a warm heart.
I want you all to never make excuses,
the way class F does.
My only regret is Irie's situation.
Someone in class F prevented
him from taking the exam.
He would've been a top ranked
applicant to Tokyo U, otherwise.
Kotoko didn't do it on purpose!
No one who would say something
like that should be a teacher.
She's right!
It's not her fault.
And it's humiliating to think anyone believes
this idiot could knock my life off course.
Humiliating? Isn't that going too far?
What part of it didn't you understand?
You're so sadistic! And cold blooded!
And yet you like me anyway.
Even gave him a love letter.
And got rejected immediately.
Sure. I get it.
If you're going to take it
this far, you must be ready.
For what?
Wait, you didn't...
Ta-da!
Get a load of Irie's baby picture!
Turns out he's got a thing for cross-dressing!
Your mom gave me another.
Get over here.
I'll love you forever.
What?
That was a hell of a stunt you pulled.
Your threats don't scare me.
How dare you make fun of my
feelings in front of everyone.
I'm done.
I give up on liking you.
You're gonna forget all about me?
That's right.
Forget all about you, find a cool guy at university and...
Good luck with that.
Serves you right.
We kissed.
I love you, Kotoko.
Really? Say it again.
Yes, of course.
Serves you right.
A dream?
Good morning.
Morning.
Have some coffee.
I brewed it myself.
I see.
Naoki, that's too plain! Why are you
wearing that dour old thing?
I put together something that matches
Kotoko's outfit for the entrance ceremony.
I am not wearing that.
See?
Right?
I'm off.
See you.
I'm off too.
See you later.
Things have been awkward since...
Kotoko.
One more step and you'll get a bloody nose.
What're you, stupid?
Hey, don't call me stupid.
You saying you're not?
You should at least ask if I'm alright.
I mean, we've kissed...
Why do you keep calling me stupid?
Can't you be nicer to me?
Huh? Did he call me Kotoko?
He did, right?
Irie, wait up!
Itazura na Kiss: High School Chapter